[OVERDO]
[Episode 25]
[Lanxin Theatre]
The Marshal is here for the opera! Clear out!
Everyone out!
Hurry up!
Out! Get out!
Go!
Let's go.
Principal Murong, there you are.
The Marshal just had the area cleared for you.
Marshal Li is truly remarkable.
I heard you've also sent an invitation to the Murong family?
Naturally.
Attachment nurtured since childhood
Runs deeper.
You brat! You kept me waiting for so long.
Sit.
What the hell is this?
So girly.
My son's returned in triumph.
Can we get something rousing?
If this is the best they've got,
They might as well not sing at all.
Guan.
Boss.
Where is Boss Hai?
Boss Hai is about to go on stage.
She doesn't have a performance today, right?
She said since Marshal Li is here,
She should show off her skills.
Oh no.
Take me there quickly.
Bravo!
She's going to kill Li Rongzhang.
Marshal Li, if she pleases you,
I'll send her over
To your residence later.
Young Marshal.
Father.
Why are you here?
Sit.
Good!
Guan, get me a hammer.
Yes.
Bravo!
Watch out!
Surround them!
No one is allowed to leave!
Not long ago,
The one who wanted to kill me
Was you,
Hai Tangqing.
Hai Tangqing?
It's me.
Father,
Is there
Some misunderstanding?
I have two good sons.
Both are afraid I'll get hurt,
So they protect me.
Great!
I'm happy today.
I've been watching shows for years,
And you're the best.
I haven't had my fill yet.
Since Hai Tangqing is here,
Then Ren Susu...
For the attack just now,
She must've tampered with the chandelier.
The only place here close to the chandelier
Is this window.
Lower your guns!
Do you still want to kill me?
Till death,
And beyond!
Very well.
I'll wait.
Ren Susu.
I know you're here.
♪ In those fleeting three seconds of twilight ♪
♪ An amber dream shimmers within the glass ♪
♪ The ice of loneliness melts away in the warmth ♪
♪ Your evasive gaze gives your heart away ♪
♪ Don't tell me ♪
♪ You're tired again, this time, don't ♪
♪ Don't push me away only to draw me close ♪
♪ Why so nervous? ♪
♪ Please don't stay frozen for too long ♪
♪ Say my name ♪
Long time no see.
♪ Please don't stop ♪
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me in a prison of your design ♪
It's been seven years.
♪ Stop bowing to the crowd ♪
How have you been
These seven years?
♪ Conquer to be free ♪
♪ Even if I'm unrepentantly obsessed ♪
As you can see,
♪ I'll let the wrongs just carry on ♪
I've been doing well at Lanxin Theatre.
♪ Drunk and unawakened, waves rage stronger ♪
♪ Let them rage, let them rise ♪
♪ Drench me through ♪
Was it you
♪ Come with me if you're brave ♪
Who tampered with the stage outside
Just now?
You want to kill Li Rongzhang,
Right?
Sometimes what you see isn't always truth.
Then tell me what is real.
♪ Again and again, knowing the danger ♪
♪ Again and again, testing the limits ♪
Ren Susu, listen.
♪ Just you and me, all else fades away ♪
Li Rongzhang's life concerns the bigger picture.
You can't kill him yet.
If you kill him...
Mom.
Where are you?
Mom, let's go.
Let's go.
She is your mom?
Then who is your dad?
I won't tell you.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Tell me,
How old are you?
I...
It hurts.
You're hurting him.
Go. Let's go back.
Le'an.
Where have you been?
Where shall we go today?
He bullied me.
Aren't you supposed to be fawning over Li Rongzhang?
What are you doing here?
I never imagined you,
The renowned
Principal Murong,
Would pick on a child.
Not your business.
It is my business.
I own this theatre.
I've heard
The boss of Lanxin Theatre
Has a wealthy patron backing her.
More than that.
She even bore him a child.
What do you mean?
Lanxin Theatre belongs to me,
And so does everyone
Inside it.
Take Le'an back first.
I have some words
To say to Qingyi in private.
Let's go.
It's been seven years.
You have changed.
You've become calmer.
If it were the past,
You wouldn't have let them go.
Enough.
Don't talk like Qingyu.
Are we close?
You left seven years ago.
The Murong family
And the Li family's mess
Fell on my shoulders.
And after Qingyu died,
The Fang family also collapsed.
She lost her protection
And almost died on the street.
I saved Miss Ren.
Miss Ren?
Who are you to call her Miss Ren?
Is it strange?
I know everything
About Susu's true identity,
And her past with you.
Why would she trust you?
Because when she was at her lowest, helpless,
I was the only one
Who reached out to her.
Because I know
She never had any real feelings for Qingyu.
Who are you to mention Qingyu in front of me?
Are you worthy?
Qingyi.
Seven years
Can change a lot of things, you know?
Those once deeply loved
Can turn into strangers.
Strangers, too,
May become companions.
You ran away for seven years.
So you'd better accept
-what happened during this period... -Nonsense!
Let me tell you, Li Boze.
The one who ran away wasn't me, but you.
Everything changed after Qingyu died.
Don't fool yourself into thinking
Things can go back to normal.
Wishful thinking.
Sure enough,
We are the ones
Who know each other best in this world.
I haven't been helping Ren Susu all these years.
I've been helping you.
Boze.
Take good care of...
Take good care of Qingyi.
The Murong family
Will always be your home.
One day you will understand.
The most important things
Must be kept with all your might.
Qingyi,
Where we are,
[Lanxin Theatre]
There is home.
You haven't left yet?
Get in the car.
Father.
The assassin who tried to kill you today
Also tried to kill you not long ago?
She stabbed at my neck with a hairpin.
This girl has a ruthless streak.
Interesting.
Then why didn't you kill her?
To keep as a plaything.
She's pretty.
I know you set up Lanxin Theatre.
You're being secretive
Just to back up this girl.
If she were just a plaything,
I wouldn't bother to interfere.
But from the look in your eyes,
It doesn't seem that way.
Don't worry.
Even if I wanted to kill her,
I wouldn't do it in front of you.
Also,
Are you sure
She is the only one in Lanxin Theatre who wants me dead?
Rest assured, Father.
No matter who means you harm,
I will protect you with my life.
Last night I had a dream
That you wanted to drink the wine from this place.
So I bought some for you today.
By the way,
Qingyi is back.
Now,
He is a renowned
General.
And he runs the aviation school well.
He has grown up.
But there is one thing
I must settle for him.
Brother,
If you were still alive,
You would back me up,
Wouldn't you?
You asked to see me.
What is it?
The matter regarding Le'an,
You haven't told Qingyi yet, have you?
Whether I tell him or not,
What's it to you?
All these years,
On top of being busy at the front,
I have also been investigating
The North-South Railway case.
I finally have some leads now.
There are some things
I think you must know.
Nineteen years ago,
Before the fire at Wucongkou Wharf,
You saved a boy, didn't you?
Help! Somebody help!
Someone's in the water!
Somebody help!
Wake up!
It hurts so bad.
I...
I feel awful.
This child...
Dad, please save him.
Don't let him die.
Something's off with this child.
He looks just like
Those opium addicts at the wharf.
He's just a child.
How could this be?
It looks like he was force-fed.
This child has a complicated background.
We can't let him stay in our home.
Then,
Where can we send him?
Send him back to the street
As if he had never been here.
No.
We can't send him away.
His parents abandoned him.
Are we going to abandon him too?
Alright, alright.
My girl.
We won't
Send him away
Until he recovers from his illness.
You haven't recovered yet.
Where are you going?
Don't follow me.
I told you not to follow me.
Don't you understand?
I saved you,
So I have to be responsible for you.
I don't care.
I didn't beg you to save me.
And now,
This boy,
You have seen him again.
What are you trying to say?
Impossible.
The boy I saved couldn't be him.
When I was investigating the Wucongkou incident,
Someone mentioned to me that
Your family saved a child back then.
It was also that year
When Qingyi left the Li family
And went missing for a few days.
After that,
Qingyu decided to bring Qingyi home
And raise him himself.
Then we were swapped back
To our respective homes.
Judging by the timeline,
This person must be Qingyi.
I know this is hard to believe.
I guess
Someone wanted to kill Qingyi
And chased him all the way to the Ren family.
And because of that fire,
A massacre
Was disguised as an accident.
After he recovered,
Qingyi only remembered
That he snuck out to deliver a message.
When he came to the Murong family,
He had been sick several times.
Due to the effects of the drugs,
His memory grew muddled.
The full facts remain unknown.
-But if you want -I don't want to know.
I finally understand
That from the moment we met,
Everything was wrong.
I came to see you,
Brother.
Don't worry.
Ms. Ye is doing well.
Over these years,
She's been running the aviation school.
When it comes to female pilots,
If she ranks second,
No one dares to claim first.
You see,
Even without you,
She's doing fine.
All these years I've been out fighting.
I've encountered many things.
And I'd always wonder
If it were you,
What you would do.
Brother.
I used to
Turn the house upside down.
And I always talked back to you.
How did you put up with it?
If it were me,
I would have given up.
It's been seven years.
They always say
I'm just like you.
Where is the resemblance?
I failed to cherish those who loved me.
As for the one I love...
Forget it.
Even without me,
She's doing fine.
Who?
Li Boze.
Why did you bring her here?
Over the years,
We've come here often.
After all,
She is family.
Family?
Whose family?
My family,
Or yours?
Why didn't you bring Le'an?
It's time to let Qingyu know
That you two have a child.
Li Boze, if you have the guts,
Admit in front of Qingyu
That the child is yours.
Do you dare?
Qingyi is right.
Boze,
It's time
For Le'an to visit his uncle.
Ren Susu!
Boze couldn't be bothered with you.
But I'm not like him.
Qingyu is Le'an's uncle.
What reason is there for us not to come?
It's not your place to force us to swear.
Do you know what shame is?
Who I am with,
And who I have a child with,
What does it have to do with you?
In all of Nancheng,
With so many men,
Why him?
Because Boze is great.
I think Qingyu would be relieved
If he knew.
Fine.
Li Boze.
You haven't changed a bit since childhood.
What I don't want,
You treat like treasure.
Whether it's treasure or not,
As the younger brother,
You are in no position to judge
Before your two elder brothers.
Why are you doing this?
He saved you after all,
And Le'an too.
I didn't beg you to save me.
I didn't beg him to save me.
Between us,
Back and forth,
Time and again,
The whys and wherefores have long been tangled.
No one can tell who was right and who was wrong.
Even if he is not the killer,
My parents are still dead.
Even if I am not the killer,
His brother is still dead.
You are a smart person.
It wasn't easy for Qingyi to get where he is today.
Now that he has completely turned things around,
Don't drag him into the abyss again.
If my brother were still alive,
He'd want you to let him go.
Do you really
Have to torture each other,
Covered in scars
That keep festering and bleeding,
To be satisfied?
Owing each other like this
Isn't good for the child.
I've made up my mind.
Le'an
Will only be my child.
Young Master Qingyi.
Are you okay?
That child definitely isn't Li Boze's.
Ren Susu lied to me.
I'm moving into Lanxin Theatre tomorrow.
Get lost if you can't do it.
How could you bear to do that?
[Lanxin Theatre]
What are you doing?
Lanxin Theatre has been temporarily requisitioned for official use.
From today onwards,
It will no longer be open to the public.
To prevent you from ruining my plan,
From now on,
You cannot leave my sight.
With me here,
The sky won't fall.
Go to the accounting office for a month's salary.
Everyone gets two weeks off.
-Yes. -Yes.
Yes.